Contact

Shartava st. Batumi, Georgia +995511306690 (Mobile) nitrosick@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nikitabuzhinskiy-2458b1255 (LinkedIn) nitrosick.eternalhost.info/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Vue.js

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Pinia

Languages

Japanese (Elementary)
English (Limited Working)

Certifications

GeekBrains Fullstack developer certificate

Nikita Buzhinskiy

Frontend developer

Batumi, Ajaria, Georgia

Summary

I got interested in programming more than 10 years ago. It all started with writing simple scripts for various computer games and programs, after which I seriously decided to master some language.

I started with learning Java. I took free online courses, but realized that I was not very good at applying my knowledge in practice. However, these courses gave me knowledge and understanding of object-oriented programming, which helps me to this day.

Later, having got acquainted with HTML and CSS, I realized that I am more interested in WEB development, as sites became almost full-fledged applications with a lot of functionality and features, and this is a huge space for imagination and self-development.

I have accumulated a number of training and test projects, including layout-based layout:

https://github.com/Nitrosick?tab=repositories.

To hone my skills, I'm building my own website:

https://hommbase.ru/

Initially it was written on pure PHP, JS, HTML and CSS without using frameworks (I implemented MVC structure, created routing and authorization, including OAuth 2.0 through social networks, made a system of tests, administrative console, as well as communication through API), then rewrote it on a more modern platform - Vue 3 + Nuxt 3 using SSR.

This link is my website - portfolio:

http://nitros66.beget.tech/

where I'm gradually putting all my projects together (I use React for frontend and PHP as backend).

In my free time I like to watch tutorial Youtube channels on web development, about fresh solutions in programming and computer repair.

Currently working as a Front-end developer with Vue and Nuxt and using them in my pet projects.

Additional resources and tools I use on a regular basis are:

- 1. Google Analytic and Yandex Metric;
- 2. W3C Validator;
- 3. Page Speed Insights;
- 4. Postman;
- 5. OpenServer;
- 6. Adobe Photoshop;
- 7. Font Awesome;
- 8. Framer Motion.

As for personal qualities: Easy to get in touch with people, I like to learn new things, I get carried away quickly and can work on interesting tasks for a long time, I like everything to be clear and according to plan, I lead an active lifestyle.

I am currently studying Japanese and plan to move to Japan and work there in the future

In addition to the phone I am always online in Telegram, nickname - @Nitrosick.

Experience

RUVENTS

Frontend Web Developer May 2023 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Moscow, Moscow City, Russia

Responsible for frontend development both for custom client orders and internal product enhancement (e.g., Eventico).

Tech Stack:

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- Vue
- Nuxt

- GraphQL
- Yarn
- Git/GitLab
- VSCode

Notable Contributions:

- Developed projects for the Platform "Movement of the First":
- "Reward of the First"

(https://xn--90ab1bi6c.xn--e1aglkf7g.xn--d1acj3b/auth/login)

(https://xn--b1agzqc8c.xn--e1aglkf7g.xn--d1acj3b/)

- "Hermitage Cat Portrait"

(https://cats.pervye.ru/)

- VOIR Fest 2024 (https://voirfest.ru/)
- Redesign of Eventico Admin Console.
- Implemented GraphQL, improving query performance and scalability.
- Built an internal PDF generator, simplifying client workflows.
- Created a GraphQL schema parser for better query handling.
- Developed CSV-based user import functionality.
- Introduced a localization mechanism for multi-language support.
- Implemented a WebSocket-based chat and support ticket system.

Baucenter

5 years 5 months

IT Support Specialist

October 2020 - January 2024 (3 years 4 months)

Kaliningrad, Russia

Key Responsibilities:

- Developed SQL scripts for large data analysis, user data management, and product catalog optimization.
- Wrote JavaScript templates for price tag generation (AzureLabel).
- Supported database operations and replication.
- Installed and configured software, ensured system stability, and managed digital signatures.

Additional Projects:

- Built a password generator app using Electron.js.
- Designed a Knowledge Base with a web interface using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

 Created a REST API application on React for employee and customer loyalty card management.

Tech stack:

- TransactSQL:
- IBExpert;
- Avarda;
- · Radmin.

Product Catalog Specialist

September 2018 - October 2020 (2 years 2 months)

Kaliningrad, Russia

Responsibilities included design of product catalog in the company's online store:

- Engaged in subject photography of merchandise in shopping centers (worked with DSLR camera and photographic equipment);
- Processed and retouched photos in Adobe Photoshop;
- Created schemes with product dimensions in Corel Draw;
- Contacted Russian and foreign suppliers to provide images and instructions of their products;
- Maintained reports on the content and relevance of the catalog.

Stack of technologies and programs used:

- Adobe Photoshop;
- · Corel Draw.

Additional to primary tasks:

- Wrote scripts for quick batch processing of photos in Photoshop, which sped up the work many times over;
- Formulated and described the requirements and standards of photos and schemes for each type of product, which the entire marketing department now works on.

Education

GeekBrains University

Fullstack Developer · (September 2020 - December 2022)